Hello everyone, in addition to the three-layer structure method mentioned earlier, the loose belt can also be used to make real counterfeits of the version.
Next, let's open the arrangement points on the model first.
Arrange the waist version on the model.
Then adjust the frame arrangement of the version in the attribute editor.
After arranging in the appropriate position, close the arrangement points on the model.
Sew the waist and skirt together.
Then, the basic line on the waist version is listed as the internal line.
Then add the elastic band version and waist version.
Add the sewing line.
And add the elastic band version to the inside of the waist version.
Next, we choose to fold the arrangement at the 3D window and fold the waist version back.
Then continue to hook the other side of the internal line.
Then fill in the sewing line.
To make the elastic band version remain in the inside of the waist version, we can use the setting layer tool.
Let the elastic band version be in the inside of the reverse waist version.
It is equivalent to the elastic band version to remain on the outside of the opposite side of the waist version.
Here is the relationship between the setting layer and the opposite side of the version.
You can check the previous video.
The setting layer is useful.
Fully understand the use of the setting layer tool.
Then, the waist version is equivalent to fixed and immobilized.
Then we can click on the elastic band version first.
Then click on the waist version.
Then change the plus button to the minus button.
The elastic band version is set to be on the opposite side of the waist version.
Open the simulation.
You can see that the waist version is very stable.
It is difficult to reach aabo because of ocupations.
The waist version is 냄 béning.
Then we choos back juice for waist version.
And improve the quality of the경具
Make the folding of the elastic band waist more細.
To increase the quality of the uniform clothing
Make the folding of the elastic band waist stand higher.
Attach at the waist of the waistourd.
So, the proper waist band already made.
Successfully misunderstood this process.
For better wind holding video.